I haven't seen my monkey in almost a year.
我已經快一年沒見到我的猴子了。
What, you never looked down in the shower?
什麼，洗澡的時候從來不低頭看嗎？
Oh, please.
哦，拜託。
I'm not allowed to make one joke in the monkey is penis genre.
我不可以在《猴子是陰莖》這一型別中開任何玩笑。
Come on, people.
來吧，人們。
Back up, please.
請備份。
Back up.
備份。
Come on, come on, come on.
來吧，來吧，來吧。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Where can we find the monkey?
我們在哪裡可以找到猴子？
I'm sorry, guys.
對不起，夥計們。
The clothes set.
衣服一套了。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
You don't understand.
你不明白。
I'm a friend of his.
我是他的朋友。
We used to live together.
我們曾經住在一起。
Yeah, and I have a time sharing the poking nose with Flipper.
是的，我也曾經和 Flipper 一起戳鼻子。
Ross, there he is.
羅斯，他在那裡。
Hey, hey, buddy.
嘿，嘿，夥計。
Marcelle, Marcelle.
瑪賽爾，瑪賽爾。
In the jungle, the mighty jungle, the lion sleeps tonight.
叢林裡，雄偉的叢林裡，獅子今晚睡著了。
A-wimbo it, a-wimbo it, a-wimbo it, a-wimbo it.
一個-溫博它，一個-溫博它，一個-溫博它，一個-溫博它。
Whee!
哎喲！
Wooo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo wee.
嗚嗚嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚。
Wooo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo wee.
嗚嗚嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚-嗚。
Ah, excuse me folks, this is a...
啊，對不起各位，這是...
Closed set, we know, but we're friends with the monkey.
我們知道，封閉集，但我們是猴子的朋友。
Good morning.
早安。
Hey, pal, look who I brought.
嘿，夥計，看看我帶來了誰。
It's your old friend, Harry Elefante.
這是你的老朋友，哈利·埃萊芬特。
I don't get it.
我不明白。
He seemed so happy to see me yesterday.
昨天他見到我似乎很高興。
Hey, don't take it personal.
嘿，別把這當成是針對個人的。
He's under a lot of pressure.
他承受著很大的壓力。
You know, starring in a movie and all.
你知道，主演電影等等。
Now, just how big of a star is Marcel?
那麼，馬塞爾到底有多偉大呢？
In human terms?
從人類的角度來說？
I'd say...
我想說...
Sibyl Shepard.
西比爾·謝潑德。
Whoa!
哇！
So, are you guys in the movie, or are you just really paranoid?
那麼，你們才是電影裡的人，還是隻是真的偏執？
Hey, Sal.
嘿，薩爾。
Jerry wants to know if the monkey's ready for the subway stop.
傑瑞想知道猴子是否準備好去地鐵站。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Jerry is the director?
導演是傑瑞？
Which one's he?
他是哪一個？
The one in the director's chair.
坐在導演椅上的人。
Gotcha.
明白了。
Pheebs, walk with him.
菲比，就跟他一起走吧。
Okay.
好的。
Um, how come I'm walking with you?
呃，我怎麼跟你走？
Well, we're just going over here so that we can get away from
好吧，我們只是到這裡來，這樣我們就可以遠離
the horrible flesh-eating virus!
可怕的食肉病毒！
For the love of God, woman, listen to me!
看在上帝的份上，女人，聽我說！
Is he looking?
他在看嗎？
We've got a problem.
我們遇到了問題。
Hi.
你好。
Tell me.
告訴我。
I can't do Chrissy's makeup.
我不會給克麗絲化妝。
She refuses to acknowledge that she has a mustache.
她拒絕承認自己有鬍子。
Is it bad?
是不是很糟糕？
It looks like one of her eyebrows fell down.
看起來，她的一根眉毛掉了下來。
Now, unless someone convinces her to let me bleach it, Jean-Claude Van
現在，除非有人說服她讓我漂白它，讓-克洛德·範
Damme's going to be making out with Gabe Kaplan.
達姆要和加布·卡普蘭親熱。
I'll talk to her.
我會和她談談。
I hate actors.
我討厭演員。
Nice camouflage, man.
很好的偽裝，夥計。
For a minute there, I almost didn't see ya.
有那麼一分鐘，我幾乎沒看到你。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Nuh-uh.
呃呃。
Uh, is your name Chandler?
呃，你叫錢德勒嗎？
Uh, yes.
呃，是的。
Yes, it is.
是的。
Chandler Vang.
錢德勒範.
Do you know me, or are you just really good at this game?
你認識我，還是你真的很擅長這個遊戲？
I'm Susie Moss.
我是蘇西·莫斯。
Fourth grade.
四年級。
Glasses.
眼鏡。
I used to carry around a box of animal crackers like a purse.
我曾經像錢包一樣隨身攜帶一盒動物餅乾。
Susie Moss?
蘇西·莫斯？
Right, yeah, wow.
對對對，哇。
You look great job growing up.
你長大後看起來工作很棒。
It's nice to see you're not still wearing that denim cap with all
很高興看到你不再戴著那頂牛仔帽
the little mirrors on it.
上面的小鏡子。
Oh, right, yeah.
哦，對了，是的。
Well, I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.
好吧，我四年級畢業，意識到我不是皮條客。
Remember the class play?
還記得課堂劇嗎？
You pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium saw my underpants.
你拉起我的裙子，整個禮堂都看到了我的內褲。
Yes, back then I used humor as a defense mechanism.
是的，當時我用幽默作為一種防衛機制。
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
感謝上帝我不再這樣做了。
So, what have you been doing since childhood?
那麼，你從小到大都在做什麼呢？
Well, um, I got a new belt.
嗯，嗯，我有一條新腰帶。
I wondered.
我想知道。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
What?
什麼？
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
這是尚格·雲頓。
I didn't know he was in this movie.
我不知道他在這部電影中。
He is so hot.
他太熱了。
You think?
您認為？
The muscles from Brussels.
來自布魯塞爾的肌肉。
Wham Bam Van Damme.
威姆‧巴姆‧範‧達姆 (Wham Bam Van Damme)。
Did you see Time Cop?
你看到《時間警察》了嗎？
No.
不。
Was he any good in it?
他有什麼好處嗎？
Rachel, he, like, totally changed time.
雷切爾，他，完全改變了時間。
Wow.
哇。
So, why don't you go talk to him?
那麼，為什麼不去跟他談談呢？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
What?
什麼？
So, you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute?
那麼，你過去告訴他你覺得他很可愛？
What's the worst that could happen?
可能發生的最壞情況是什麼？
He could hear me.
他聽得見我說話。
Okay, I'm doing it for you.
好吧，我正在為你做。
Oh, Rachel, don't!
哦，雷切爾，別這樣！
Don't you dare!
你不敢！
Don't!
不！
Tell him I cook!
告訴他我煮飯！
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Hi.
你好。
Um, this is gonna sound kind of goofy, but, um, my friend over
嗯，這聽起來有點傻，但是，嗯，我的朋友結束了
there, who cooks, by the way, um, she thinks you're cute.
在那裡，誰做飯，順便說一句，嗯，她認為你很可愛。
You don't think I'm cute?
你不覺得我可愛嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Um, you think you're cute?
Okay, we're kind of getting off the track here.
好吧，我們有點偏離軌道了。
Um, I was supposed to come here and tell you my friend thinks
嗯，我應該來這裡告訴你我朋友的想法
you're cute.
你很可愛。
So, what should I tell her?
那麼，我該告訴她什麼呢？
You can tell her I think her friend is cute.
Now, Stephen Hurs was the kid who would eat anything for money.
現在，史蒂芬‧赫斯是個為了錢什麼都願意吃的孩子。
David Stein was the guy who had no elbows.
Okay, well, then, who was the kid that got caught masturbating?
好吧，那麼，那個自慰被發現的孩子是誰？
Okay, that's not what he was doing, all right?
好吧，他不是這麼做的，好嗎？
He was looking for his bus money.
他正在尋找他的公車錢。
Oh, that's me.
哦，那就是我。
I gotta go.
我得走了。
Oh, um...
哦，嗯...
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Um, so, listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you
嗯，所以，聽著，我要碰你多少次
on the arm before you ask me on a date?
在你約我約會之前在手臂上？
Well, uh, let's try one more.
好吧，呃，我們再試一次。
There you go, St. Ernie's, 8 o'clock.
就這樣，聖厄尼教堂，八點鐘。
I'll be there.
我會在那裡。
And who knows, if things go well, maybe this time I'll get to
誰知道呢，如果一切順利的話，也許這次我會到達
see your underwear.
看你的內衣。
No one was around to hear that.
周圍沒有人聽到這句話。
So, what'd he say?
那麼，他說什麼？
Oh, what a jerk.
哦，真是個混蛋。
I kept talking about you.
我一直在談論你。
And he kept asking me out.
他一直約我出去。
I mean, naturally.
我的意思是，自然地。
I said no.
我說不。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Thanks anyway.
不管怎樣，謝謝。
He just kept asking.
他只是不停地問。
Asking, asking, asking, asking, asking.
問，問，問，問，問。
Rachel, if you want to go out with him, you can.
雷切爾，如果你想和他出去，你可以。
I mean, sounds like a big jerk to me, but if that's what
我的意思是，對我來說聽起來像個大混蛋，但如果是這樣的話
you want to do...
你想做...
Jon Quach, he said yes!
喬恩·誇奇，他說是的！
I'll see you tonight!
今晚見！
Thank you.
謝謝。
And then, Jon-Claude took me to that place, Crossroads, and that's where
然後，喬恩-克勞德帶我去了那個地方，十字路口，那就是那裡
we hung out with Drew Barrymore.
我們和德魯·巴里摩爾一起出去玩。
Oh, man, she's so smokin'.
哦，夥計，她抽煙太厲害了。
She's got the greatest set of...
她擁有最偉大的一套...
No guys around, huh?
周圍沒有人吧？
Does anybody need anything?
有人需要什麼嗎？
Oh, I'll have an espresso.
哦，我要一杯濃縮咖啡。
Oh, actually, I'll get it.
哦，實際上，我會得到它。
If I ask you to, you'll probably end up drinking it yourself.
如果我要求你喝，你可能最終會自己喝掉。
That is so unfair.
那太不公平了。
I know.
我知道。
Like you would drink her coffee after what you did to her with
就像你對她做了什麼之後你會喝她的咖啡一樣
Van Damme?
範達姆？
Hey, Joey, I have to cancel Racquetball for tonight.
嘿，喬伊，我必須取消今晚的壁球比賽。
That was Marcel's trainer.
那是馬塞爾的教練。
He's gonna let me have him for a couple of hours.
他會讓我陪他幾個小時。
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
你把我當作一隻猴子來嘲笑我嗎？
Hey, we can reschedule for Saturday.
嘿，我們可以改期到週六。
Yeah, unless you hook up with a bunch of pigeons.
是的，除非你和一群鴿子勾搭上。
Hey, stick a fork in me.
嘿，把叉子插在我身上。
I am done.
我完成了。
Stick a fork what?
叉子插什麼？
Like when you're cooking a steak.
就像你煮牛排時一樣。
Oh, okay, I don't eat meat.
哦，好吧，我不吃肉。
Well, then, how do you know when vegetables are done?
那麼，你怎麼知道蔬菜什麼時候熟了呢？
Well, you don't.
好吧，你不知道。
You just...
你只是...
you eat them, and you can tell.
你吃了它們，你就知道了。
Okay, then eat me.
好吧，那就吃我吧。
I'm done.
我受夠了。
I've met the perfect woman.
我遇到了完美的女人。
Okay, we're sitting on her couch, we're fooling around, and then, suddenly, she
好吧，我們坐在她的沙發上，我們正在閒逛，然後，突然，她
turns to me and says, Do you ever want to do it in
轉向我說，你想在
an elevator?
電梯？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What did you say?
你說什麼？
I believe my exact words were, I mean, I didn't know what to
我相信我的原話是，我的意思是，我不知道該做什麼
say.
說。
How do you know if you want to do it on an elevator?
你怎麼知道你是否想在電梯上做這件事？
Oh, you just know.
哦，你才知道。
Mmm.
嗯。
Oh, shoot, we gotta go.
哦，射擊，我們得走了。
Got a reservation at 30 minutes.
30分鐘後就預約到了。
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
噢，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
You see, what I had planned shouldn't take more than two three-minutes
你看，我計畫的時間不會超過兩三分鐘
tops.
最高額。
200 seconds of passion.
200秒的激情。
We gotta go.
我們得走了。
But, um...
但是，嗯...
Here's an idea.
這是一個想法。
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
你穿過女士內衣嗎？
Well, yes, actually.
嗯，是的，實際上。
But, uh, they were my Aunt Edna's.
但是，呃，它們是我愛德娜阿姨的。
And there were three of us in there.
那裡有我們三個人。
Well, I was thinking it would be, um, kind of sexy if you
嗯，我在想，嗯，如果你這麼做的話，會有點性感
wore mine tonight at dinner.
今晚晚餐時穿著我的。
You want me to wear your panties?
你要我穿你的內褲嗎？
Could you?
您可以...嗎？
Well, if I was wearing your underwear, then, uh, what would you be
好吧，如果我穿著你的內衣，那麼，呃，你會是什麼樣子
wearing?
穿著？
You're swell.
你膨脹了。
Okay, got the music, got the dinner.
好吧，聽音樂，吃晚餐。
Oh, and check it out, I made Marcel's favorite dish, banana cake.
哦，看看，我做了馬塞爾最喜歡的菜，香蕉蛋糕。
Ooh.
哦。
With mealworms.
與麵包蟲。
Ah, candle.
啊，蠟燭。
What do you think's gonna happen here tonight?
你覺得今晚這裡會發生什麼事？
Hello?
你好？
Oh, hi, are you on your way over?
哦，嗨，你正在過來嗎？
Oh.
哦。
No, no, I understand.
不，不，我明白。
I mean, a monkey's gotta work.
我的意思是，猴子必須工作。
No, it's no big deal.
不，沒什麼大不了的。
It's not like I, uh, had anything special planned.
我並沒有，呃，有什麼特別的計劃。
You know.
你知道。
Yeah, okay.
是啊，好吧。
Okay, okay, bye.
好吧好吧，再見。
I'm sorry, man.
對不起，夥計。
Yeah.
是的。
You feel that?
你感覺到了嗎？
What?
什麼？
That we passed the moment when we should have stopped holding hands?
我們已經過了本該停止牽手的時刻了嗎？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Okay, Rachel, why don't you start talking first?
好吧，雷切爾，你為什麼不先開始說話呢？
All right.
好的。
I feel that this is totally unjustified.
我覺得這是完全沒有道理的。
She gave me the green light, I did nothing wrong.
她給了我綠燈，我沒有做錯任何事。
Do you think I can't see you in the TV set?
你以為我在電視上看不見你嗎？
All right, Monica, if there is something that you would like to share,
好吧，莫妮卡，如果你有什麼想分享的，
You know, you had no right to go out with him.
你知道，你沒有權利跟他出去。
That is the most ridiculous thing.
這是最可笑的事。
You sold me out.
你出賣了我。
I did not say you would.
我沒說你會的。
Yes, you did.
是的，你做到了。
Absolutely sold me.
絕對把我賣了。
Would you let me talk?
你能讓我談談嗎？
Did you just flick me?
你剛才是不是甩了我？
Okay, well, you wouldn't let me finish, and I was...
好吧，好吧，你不讓我說完，而我...
Ow, that hurt!
哎呀，好痛啊！
Quick flicking!
快閃啊！
Ow, you!
哎呀，你！
Stop flicking!
別再抖了！
You flicked me first!
是你先打我的！
Ow!
噢！
Stop it!
停下來！
Ow!
噢！
Stop it!
停下來！
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
No, no, let's not do this.
不，不，我們不要這樣做。
Let's not do this.
我們不要這樣做。
Come on!
快點！
Stop it!
停下來！
Okay, now I'm gonna kick some ass!
好吧，現在我要踢一些屁股了！
Ow!
噢！
All right, now I will let go if you both stop.
好吧，如果你們都停下來，我就放手了。
What do you...
你做什麼...
You want me to stop seeing him?
你想讓我不再見到他嗎？
Is that what you want?
這就是你想要的嗎？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
You want me to just call him up and tell him that you're
你想讓我打電話給他並告訴他你
seeing him instead.
而是看到他。
Is that what you want?
這就是你想要的嗎？
Okay.
好的。
Oh, that's what you want?
噢，這就是你想要的？
Yes.
是的。
Fine.
美好的。
There we go.
我們開始吧。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
If we were in prison, you guys would be like my bitches.
如果我們在監獄裡，你們就會像我的母狗一樣。
Thanks for letting me tag along tonight, you guys.
謝謝你們讓我今晚陪我，你們。
Forget about it.
忘記它吧。
How you doing there, squirmy?
你在那裡過得怎麼樣，蠕動？
I'm hanging in.
我還掛著呢
And a little out.
還有一點。
So, assistant to the director.
那麼，導演助理。
That's a really exciting job.
這真是一項令人興奮的工作。
I mean, you must have a ton of cool responsibilities.
我的意思是，你必須承擔很多很酷的責任。
I have nothing to do with casting.
我與選角無關。
So what are you guys gonna eat?
那你們要吃什麼？
How come all I can think about is putting that ice in my
為什麼我只想著把冰放進我的
mouth and licking you all over?
嘴舔你全身？
Because I went to an all-boys high school and God is making
因為我去了一所男子高中，而上帝正在創造
up for it?
準備好了嗎？
I want you right here, right now.
我想要你就在這裡，現在。
Right now, right here?
現在，就在這裡？
Don't you think we're in kind of a public play?
你不覺得我們正在上演一場公共戲劇嗎？
They do have the shrimp.
他們確實有蝦。
Oh.
哦。
Meet me in the bathroom.
在浴室見我。
I'm going to the bathroom now.
我現在去趟洗手間。
He likes to keep us in the loop.
他喜歡讓我們瞭解最新情況。
Come on.
快點。
I can't believe we're doing this.
我不敢相信我們正在這樣做。
All right, mister.
好吧，先生。
Let's see those panties.
讓我們看看那些內褲。
All righty.
好吧。
Ooh.
哦。
But you know what would be even sexier?
但你知道什麼會更性感嗎？
What?
什麼？
If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.
如果你沒有把襯衫塞進裡面。
Oh.
哦。
All right.
好的。
Now, I would like to see you wearing nothing but them.
現在，我希望看到你只穿它們。
Take your clothes off.
把你的衣服脫掉。
Okay.
好的。
But I hope you realize this means we're going to miss hearing about
但我希望你意識到這意味著我們將錯過聽到
the specials.
特價菜。
Come on, hurry, hurry.
來吧，快點，快點。
Hey, do you want this done quick or do you want it done
嘿，你想要快速完成還是想完成
right?
正確的？
All right, turn around.
好吧，轉身吧。
I will see you from behind.
我會從後面看到你。
Oh, somebody's been doing his Bones of Steel video.
哦，有人在製作他的《Bones of Steel》影片。
So, you want me to, uh, clench anything or...
所以，你希望我，呃，握緊任何東西，或...
Susie?
蘇西？
This is for the fourth grade.
這是四年級的。
Huh?
啊？
Wait, what do you mean?
等等，你什麼意思？
What do I mean?
我是什麼意思？
What do you mean, what do I mean?
你什麼意思，我什麼意思？
I mean, underpants, mister.
我是說，內褲，先生。
That's what I mean.
這就是我的意思。
What?
什麼？
What's what you mean?
你的意思是什麼？
My skirt.
我的裙子。
You lifted kids laughing?
你讓孩子們笑起來了嗎？
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18.
18 歲前我都是 Susie Underpants。
That was in the fourth grade.
那是四年級的時候。
How could you still be upset about that?
你怎麼還能為此感到不安呢？
Well, um, why don't you call me in 20 years and tell me
嗯，20年後你為什麼不打電話告訴我
if you're still upset about this?
如果你還為此感到不安嗎？
I hope you realize you're not getting these underpants back.
我希望你意識到你無法拿回這些內褲。
I can't believe this.
我簡直不敢相信這一點。
Just like two weeks ago I was watching Sudden Death and now I'm
就像兩週前我在看《突然死亡》，現在我
on a date with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
與尚格·雲頓 (Jean-Claude Van Damme) 約會。
Can you beat up that guy?
你能打敗那傢伙嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Can you beat up that guy?
你能打敗那傢伙嗎？
Sure.
當然。
This is so wild.
這太狂野了。
You know, I gotta admit, I was kind of surprised that you agreed
你知道，我必須承認，你同意我有點驚訝
to go on a blind date.
去相親。
Normally I would not do it.
通常我不會這樣做。
Yeah?
是的？
Well, what made you make the exception for me?
那麼，是什麼讓你為我破例呢？
Because Rachel told me you were dying to have a threesome with me
因為瑞秋告訴我你很想跟我一起三人行
and Drew Barrymore.
和德魯·巴里摩爾。
Oh, by the way, Drew has some ground rules.
哦，順便說一句，德魯有一些基本規則。
Say you're sorry!
說聲對不起！
No!
不！
Say it, Rachel!
說吧，雷切爾！
No!
不！
Please don't say it!
請不要說出來！
Say it!
說吧！
Rachel, you say you're sorry or your sweater gets it.
雷切爾，你說你很抱歉，否則你的毛衣就被汙染了。
Okay, okay, that is my favorite sweater.
好吧好吧，這是我最喜歡的毛衣。
That is my third date sweater.
那是我的第三件約會毛衣。
Say you're sorry.
說聲對不起。
Okay, you wanna play?
好吧，你想玩嗎？
Okay, let's play.
好吧，讓我們來玩吧。
Let's play.
讓我們玩。
What are you gonna do?
你要做什麼？
You give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara?
你把我的毛衣還給我還是把手提包 marinara 還給我？
You don't have the guts.
你沒這個膽量。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
Well, at least I wasn't too chicken to tell some guy I thought
好吧，至少我還沒有膽小到不敢告訴某個我認為的人
he was cute.
他很可愛。
Oh!
哦！
Oh, all right, stop!
哦，好吧，停下來！
Stop the madness!
停止瘋狂吧！
This is crazy!
這太瘋狂了！
Who can even remember why you started fighting in the first place?
誰還記得你們最初為什麼開始打架？
She knew that if I joined my team, she would have been the
她知道如果我加入我的團隊，她就會成為
one who was beaten in the head first!
一個先被打到頭部的人！
Yes, that's right.
是的，沒錯。
But still, I...
但即便如此，我...
Look at your purse!
看看你的錢包！
Look at your sweater!
看看你的毛衣！
Look at yourselves!
看看你們自己吧！
I'll help you fix your sweater.
我會幫你修理你的毛衣。
I'll help you throw out your purse.
我會幫你扔掉你的錢包。
I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.
很抱歉我讓你不再見到他了。
Well, I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked
好吧，我很抱歉當我知道你喜歡的時候我就和他出去了
him.
他。
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
很抱歉借用了你的手套。
Joey?
喬伊？
Ma?
媽？
Chandler?
錢德勒？
What are you still doing here?
你還在這裡做什麼？
I thought you guys took off.
我以為你們已經起飛了
Oh, no, no, no, she took off.
噢，不，不，不，她走了。
With my clothes!
和我的衣服一起！
Are you naked in there?
你在裡面赤身裸體嗎？
Well, not exactly.
嗯，不完全是。
I'm wearing panties.
我穿著內褲。
Huh.
呵呵。
You, uh...
你，呃…
You always wear panties?
你總是穿內褲嗎？
No, no.
不，不。
This is the first time.
這是第一次。
Wow.
哇。
Talk about your bad luck.
談談你的黴運。
Hey, the first time you try panties and someone walks off with your
嘿，當你第一次嘗試內褲時，有人拿著你的內褲走開了
clothes.
衣服。
I was not trying them out.
我並沒有嘗試它們。
Susie asked me to wear them.
蘇西讓我穿上它們。
Well, let me see.
好吧，讓我看看。
No.
不。
I'm not letting you or anybody else see, ever.
我永遠不會讓你或任何人看到。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Someone's flossing.
有人在用牙線。
Joey?
喬伊？
Some people don't like that.
有些人不喜歡這樣。
Chandler's wearing panties.
錢德勒穿著內褲。
What?
什麼？
Let me see.
讓我看看。
No, no, you have to see.
不，不，你必須看看。
Hi, Tushy.
嗨，圖希。
All right.
好的。
Why don't you give me your underpants?
為什麼不把你的內褲給我？
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
I can't help you.
我幫不了你。
I'm not wearing any.
我什麼都沒穿
How can you not be wearing any underwear?
怎麼可以不穿內衣呢？
Oh, I'm getting heat from the guy in the hot pink car.
哦，我從那輛粉紅色汽車裡的傢伙身上感到很熱。
All right, look, Ross, I'll give you $50 for your underpants.
好吧，羅斯，我給你 50 美元買你的內褲。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, Pheebs, can I have
嘿，菲比，我可以嗎
the milk after you?
牛奶在你之後嗎？
I'm almost done with it.
我快完成了。
Keep your panties on.
穿上你的內褲。
All right.
好的。
Hey, hey, and I'm in the movie.
嘿，嘿，我在電影裡。
Hey!
嘿！
One of the virus victims called in sick, so Kathy recommended me, and
一名病毒受害者請病假，所以凱西推薦了我，然後
boom, I'm dying on a gurney.
繁榮，我快死在輪床上了。
Hey!
嘿！
Oh, Ross, Marcel just finished his last scene.
哦，羅斯，馬塞爾剛剛完成他的最後一幕。
If you want to go down there and say goodbye.
如果你想去那裡告別。
Uh, no, that's okay.
呃，不，沒關係。
I mean, he's probably got, you know, parties to go to and stuff.
我的意思是，你知道，他可能要去參加派對之類的。
You know, he's moved on.
你知道，他已經繼續前進了。
Hey, that's the way it goes, right?
嘿，事情就是這樣，對吧？
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
What?
什麼？
I'm sorry it didn't work out between you and me.
很抱歉你和我之間沒有結果。
Or you and me.
或者你和我。
Drew was very disappointed.
德魯非常失望。
Oh.
哦。
Okay, well, fine.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
Goodbye.
再見。
Well, bye from me, too.
好吧，我也再見了。
Okay, well, bye-bye again.
好吧，好吧，再次再見。
Okay.
好的。
Perhaps the three of us just could...
也許我們三個人可以...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Are you sure?
你確定嗎？
I can crush a walnut with my butt.
我可以用屁股壓碎核桃。
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Impressive, but no.
令人印象深刻，但沒有。
Maybe if I were baking.
也許如果我在烘焙的話。
Okay.
好的。
Bye-bye.
再見。
Bye, Marcel.
再見，馬塞爾。
See you on the big screen.
大螢幕上見。
You keep people drinking that beer, okay?
你讓人們喝那種啤酒，好嗎？
We'll miss you, buddy.
我們會想念你的，夥計。
You know, I think I want to write a song about all this.
你知道，我想我想寫一首關於這一切的歌。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Ooh, except one of the strings on my guitar is broken.
哦，除了我吉他上的一根弦斷了。
Hey, Chandler, can I borrow your G-string?
嘿，錢德勒，我可以藉你的丁字褲嗎？
How long have you been waiting to say that?
你等這句話等了多久了？
About 20 minutes.
大約20分鐘。
Can't you see what's going on here?
你看不到這裡發生了什麼事嗎？
This man is dying!
這個男人快死了！
Ah!
啊!
Cut!
切！
Can't you see what's going on here?
你看不到這裡發生了什麼事嗎？
This man is dying!
這個男人快死了！
Ah!
啊!
Cut!
切！
Can't you see what's going on here?
你看不到這裡發生了什麼事嗎？
This man is dying!
這個男人快死了！
Ah!
啊!
Mommy!
媽媽！
Can't you see what's going on?
你看不出發生了什麼事嗎？
This man is dead!
這個人死了！